Erin Blaize

5117 N. Bristol ~ Tacoma, Wa. 98047 ~ (206) 697-2114 ~ <u>eeblaize2@hotmail.com</u>

Interested in applying for the Human Resource Coordinator position, in order to gain experience and further my knowledge in the human resources and administrative field. I desire to join a team-centered workplace environment where I could utilize my experience in administrative, clerical, data entry, and customer service background along with my strong multi-tasking capabilities, problem solving, organizational skills, and knowledge gained through college course work in human resource management.

Education

January 2021 to Current University of Washington Certificate in Computer Programming

September 2016 to January 2020 Baker College of Owosso Completing Bachelors of Business Administration Degree with a concentration in Human Resource Management with a Medical Office Minor.

September 1995 to June 1999 James A. Garfield High School Graduate - High School Diploma

Skills & Abilities

- Accomplished in performing multiple tasks, diverse projects, meeting deadlines with attention to detail in a fast-paced environment.
- Proficient in organizing projects and working within groups to ensure the efficient completion of organizational goals.
- Excellent problem solving skills, and with executing and following through on projects to completion.
- Able to work with and handle sensitive and confidential material.
- Strong writing and documentation skills.
- Strong customer service skills and vast experience dealing with a wide variety of personalities.
- Excellent communication skills. Able to clearly communicate and meet set expectations.
- Able to recognize and fill in deficiencies without prompting. Eager to learn new skills.
- Proficient with Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint
- 68 WPM
- Data-entry
- Filing
- 10 key by touch
- Appointments
- Google Docs
- Enterprise systems

Professional Experience

Part-time Student, January 2021 to current

University of Washington

Currently enrolled in certificate course in computer programming.

Bookkeeper, March 2019 to January 2021

Cambridge Management Inc., Tacoma, WA.

Responsible for bookkeeping for multiple housing properties. Work in conjunction with apartment management to maintain resident's ledgers. Keep banking reconciled and work on all accounts receivables for properties.

Part-Time Student, September 2016 to January 2020

Full-time student working on bachelor's degree in business with a concentration in human resource management and a medical office minor.

Office Worker, September, 2015 to September, 2016 – 40 to 45 hrs per week

Maurer Heating and Cooling, Owosso, MI

Responsible for service billing, answering phone calls, scheduling appointments, data entry, and problem-solving customer billing questions. In addition, handled counter sales, special projects from business owner, and additional office work.

Work-study, September, 2012 to October 2014 – 20 hrs per week

Baker College of Owosso, Owosso, MI

Responsible for answering phone calls, taking messages, making appointments, data entry, and routing calls to various campus departments. In addition, worked to direct student traffic through the Academic Resource center and campus while providing excellent customer service to students and staff. Completing data-entry, special projects and work as assigned by advisors and Office Manager.

Temporary Work, June 2012 to August 2012 – Worked on as needed basis

Temporary hire, Seattle, Washington

Employed for a temporary position doing administrative duties for an independent sales representative of Aflac. Responsibilities were: Creating packets with Aflac information for presentations, sorting pamphlets, and creating mailing envelopes.

Americorps Volunteer, September 2011 to May 2012 – 30 to 40 hrs per week Americorps, Tacoma, Washington

Employed as a Washington Reading Corps reading specialist in an elementary school in Tacoma. Responsibilities were: tutoring children that were struggling with their reading and writing, assisting teachers with small reading groups and providing additional clerical support, as well as providing support with the planning and execution of school reading events.

Animal Caregiver, May 2009 to September 2011 – Worked on as needed basis

Self-employed, Issaquah, Washington

Provided daily and extended care for client's animals. Responsibilities included: walking, feeding, and providing any additional care needed for cats, dogs, and other small animals.

Sales Consultant, September 2008 to April 2009 – 20 to 30 hrs per week Lane, Bryant, Issaquah, Washington

Responsibilities: assist customers with finding outfits and sizes as well as work the register and answer phone calls. Provided excellent customer service in a fast-paced sales environment.

Customer Liason, April 2007 to January 2008 – 40 hrs per week Owest Communications, Seattle, Washington

Responsibilities were to handle inbound calls, and work with the overdue accounts to arrange a payment plan to fit the needs of the company and clients.

Additional Work Experience

Groomer, PetSmart, January 2007 to April 2007, Tukwila, Washington
HMSA Insurance (temp position), September 2006 to December 2006, Honolulu, Hawaii
Certified Pet Groomer, February 2006 to August 2006, Petco, Issaquah, Washington
Certified Pet Groomer, January 2005 to January 2006, Company, Issaquah, Washington
Radiology Clerk, November 2000 to January 2005, Virginia Mason Hospital, Seattle, Washington